<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
    <template id="about_us_test" name="About Us">
        <t t-call="website.layout">
            <div id="wrap" class="oe_structure oe_empty">
                <div class="lookbook">
                    <div class="container">
                        <div class="lookbookSection">
                            <h1>About Us</h1>
                        </div>  
                    </div>
                </div>
                <div class="aboutpagetitle">
                    <div class="container">
                        <div class="aboutpagetitleinner text-center">
                            <p class="aboutsubtitle">#WEARESMILINGROCKS</p>
                            <p>Spread the Chain of Smile to Everyone from Lab to Home to community.</p>
                            <h2>DIAMONDS ARE FOR EVERYONE®.</h2>
                            <div class="leftTextrightImage">
                                <div class="leftText">
                                    <h2 class="mb-3">Wear a Smile</h2>
                                    <p  class="mb-3">We want you to find reasons to smile in your everyday, from the time leaving your house to the endless experience of the day, we want you to be comfortable and confident wearing Smiling Rocks. Our unique designs and one-of-a-kind styles will bring your personality to a different level. Our sustainable, affordable and conflict-free lab grown diamond jewelry is perfect for your pocket! Love who you are, the way you look and the way you smile.</p>
                                </div>
                                <div class="rightImage">
                                    <img alt="img" src="/website_sr/static/src/images/aboutinner1.jpg" />
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="leftImagerightText">
                                <div class="leftImage">
                                    <img alt="img" src="/website_sr/static/src/images/aboutinner2.jpg" />
                                </div>
                                <div class="rightText">
                                    <h2 class="mb-3">Why we Smile</h2>
                                    <p  class="mb-3">Our goal is to put luxury, transparency and responsible sourcing in our utmost priority. Our lab grown diamond are 100% identical to mind diamonds and much kinder to the earth. We want you to participate in our #giveback journey. 10% of your purchase is donated to your choice of charity. We want you to feel the power of Feeling Good while Doing Good.</p>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>  
                </div>
                <div class="founder">
                    <div class="container">
                        <div class="founderSection text center">
                            <h2>Our Founder</h2>
                            <p>We are on a mission to make this world a better place by first starting with us and our business. Zulu Ghevriya is a self-made businessman with over 20 years of experience in the Diamond and Jewelry Industry. Our Lab Man have built this business as an embodiment of his dream and a lifetime goal. He has seen this industry strive but did not feel 100% satisfied with his accomplishment. He wanted to do something for the world, so that he can leave a positive footprint for the next generations. Smiling Rocks is a brand they built that promotes the betterment in communities and preserve our mother nature. He believes Smiling Rocks is the links for the smiles that will pass from the lab to the world.</p>
                            <img class="founderImage" alt="founder" src="/website_sr/static/src/images/founder.jpg" />
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
                <div class="founder">
                    <div class="container">
                        <div class="founderSection text center">
                            <h2>Smiling Rocks Brand Story</h2>
                            <p>A journey of our diamonds, our mission and our passion with your support and purchase. Watch a short video about us and our mission that we promised together with you. </p>
                            <img class="founderImage" alt="founder" src="/website_sr/static/src/images/video-thumb.jpeg" />
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
                <div class="contact">
                    <div class="container">
                        <div class="contactusForm">
                            <h2>Contact Us For More Information</h2>
                            <form action="#" method="post">
                                <div class="form-group flex-container">
                                    <input type="text" name="first_name" placeholder="First Name" />
                                    <input type="text" name="last_name" placeholder="Last Name" />
                                </div>
                                <div class="form-group flex-container">
                                    <input type="text" name="email_address" placeholder="Email Address" />
                                    <input type="text" name="phone_number" placeholder="Phone Number" />
                                </div>
                                <div class="form-group">
                                    <textarea name="message" rows="5" placeholder="Message"></textarea>
                                </div>
                                <div class="form-group">
                                    <a href="#" class="button arrow" type="submit" value="Submit">SUBMIT</a>
                                </div>
                            </form>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>  
        </t>
    </template>
    
    
    
    <record id="about_page" model="website.page">
        <field name="name">About Us</field>
        <field name="is_published" eval="True"/>
        <field name="url">/pages/about-us-lab-grown-diamond</field>
        <field name="header_overlay" eval="True"/>
        <field name="view_id" ref="about_us_test"/>
        <field name="track" eval="True"/>
    </record>
</odoo>