<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
    <template id="faq_test" name="Frequently Asked Questions">
        <t t-call="website.layout">
            <div id="wrap" class="oe_structure oe_empty">
                <div class="lookbook">
                    <div class="container">
                        <div class="lookbookSection">
                            <h1>Frequently Asked Questions</h1>
                        </div>  
                    </div>
                </div>

                <div class="faqsection">
                    <div class="container">
                        <div class="faqsectionInner">
                            <div class="firstpoint">
                                <div class="poinTitle">
                                    <h2>Smiling Rocks World</h2>
                                </div>
                                <div class="detail">
                                    <div class="oandD">
                                        <p class="pque">How Are Smiling Rocks diamonds made?</p>
                                        <p>Lab-grown diamonds are diamonds with the same crystal structure, chemical composition, and physical properties as the mined rocks: carbon atoms arranged in a cubic crystal structure. They are grown in labs, with advanced technological processes that stimulate the same conditions under which mined diamonds develop when they form in the mantle, beneath the Earth’s crust</p>
                                        <p>Here at Smiling Rocks we proudly offer only laboratory-grown, socially and environmentally conscious diamonds in our fine jewelry.</p>
                                        <p>This makes our diamonds brighter, and stronger and more responsible. Our diamonds are dedicated to sustainable smiles.</p>
                                    </div>
                                    <div class="oandD">
                                        <p class="pque">Cs of Smiling Rocks</p>
                                        <p>Here in Smiling rocks, we believe in building a chain of smile with our Customers, Colleagues, Community, because we Care.</p>
                                        <p>To get more detailed information please visit Our Diamonds page.</p>
                                    </div>
                                    <div class="oandD">
                                        <p class="pque">Is my diamond Laser Inscribed?</p>
                                        <p>Yes, all Smiling Rocks diamonds are laser-inscribed with our logo. Also, if you are purchasing a loose diamond, that's one carat up, the stones will be inscribed with an IGI certification number.</p>
                                    </div>
                                    <div class="oandD">
                                        <p class="pque">I’d like to purchase loose diamonds in large quantity, how can I do so?</p>
                                        <p>If you are interested in working with us, please contact order@smilingrocks.com and we will assist your requests accordingly.</p>
                                    </div>
                                    <div class="oandD">
                                        <p class="pque">Can I choose to donate with each purchase?</p>
                                        <p>Yes, we have set up a channel for the charitable distribution of funds so that 10% of the proceeds from your purchase is contributed to Smiling Rocks Foundation, Inc. (the “Foundation”). The Foundation will be responsible for dispersing the funds to the specific charities that you choose when making a purchase from the website. While 10% of your purchase is ultimately contributed to the charitable organizations, tax deductions are not available to each individual customer since the customer’s donations are not directly contributed.</p>
                                    </div>
                                    <div class="oandD">
                                        <p class="pque">What are the charity sectors I can donate to?</p>
                                        <p>You can choose for the Foundation to disperse the donation funds from your purchase to the following 4 charity sectors: Medical Support, Environmental Support,  Social Support, and Animal Protection. Check out more via our Impact Page.</p>
                                    </div>     
                                    <div class="oandD">
                                        <p class="pque">Can I choose the % of my donation?</p>
                                        <p>Yes, all customers may choose between our 4 designated charity sectors, mentioned above, and decide on which portion of the funds (collectively equal to 10% of the customer’s purchase), will be directed to a certain charity sector(s) by the Foundation. For clarity purposes, the customer is in control of where the funds will be dispersed, and the Foundation will disperse the funds accordingly.</p>
                                    </div>                                  
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="firstpoint">
                                <div class="poinTitle">
                                    <h2>Shipping and Returns</h2>
                                </div>
                                <div class="detail">
                                    <div class="oandD">
                                        <p class="pque">Where do you ship?</p>
                                        <p>We ship all over the USA only. International shipping is not available at the moment. To make sure all items are delivered safely, we offer UPS and FedEx standard shipping. Please note that we require a signature upon delivery.</p>
                                    </div>
                                    <div class="oandD">
                                        <p class="pque">What does shipping cost?</p>
                                        <p>IT'S FREE! We offer free shipping to all orders.</p>
                                    </div>
                                    <div class="oandD">
                                        <p class="pque">I haven’t received my package. How can I track my order?</p>
                                        <p>You can track your package with DHL or FedEx. If you see any issue with your delivery, please contact our support team at order@smilingrocks.com and we will get on the case.</p>
                                    </div>
                                    <div class="oandD">
                                        <p class="pque">What is the return policy?</p>
                                        <p>Jewelry Return Policy</p>
                                        <p>We offer free returns within 30 days of item delivery. Items must be in their original condition, with tags intact and unworn. It should be returned in their original packaging as shipped. Smiling Rocks reserves the right to reject any returns that do not meet the conditions specified above. In such case, we will return these items to you. If items are found faulty or defective, it should be returned in their original packaging. Items with special order or request are not returnable.</p>
                                        <p>Diamond Return Policy</p>
                                        <p>We offer free returns within 30 days of item delivery. If you wish to return, the diamond must be in its original condition and shipped with the grading reports. If the diamond report is not returned, you will be charged for $150 USD as a replacement cost. Please return the diamond in its original packaging as shipped. Once received, we will need to inspect the diamond (it will take a week). Smiling Rocks reserves the right to reject the diamonds if it is not returned in its original condition. You will be notified once the return process is approved or rejected. The rejected items will be sent back to your original shipping address.</p>
                                        <p>In order to process a return of your purchased items simply send us an email to order@smilingrocks.com.</p>
                                        <p>The following exclusions that will not be accepted as a manufacturing defect and applied to the return and refund policy include:</p>
                                        <ul>
                                            <li>Precious metals change of color due to exposure from chemicals, used while swimming and hot tubs or bathing.</li>
                                            <li>Any items with bent prongs due to daily wear and requiring a refurbishment.</li>
                                            <li>Due to daily wear, stones to fall out as prongs get worn out.</li>
                                            <li>Missing stones or lost stones due to daily wear or any kinds of damage.</li>
                                            <li>Any special orders are not returnable or refundable.</li>    
                                        </ul>
                                    </div> 
                                    <div class="oandD">
                                        <p class="pque">How do I return an item?</p>
                                        <p>At the time of your return request, we will send you a prepaid FedEx return label. Please include the copy of your original dispatch document inside the box, and make sure that all your personal details are filled on the dispatch. Make sure to receive a proof of postage from the FedEx office when you ship back your item. We will not be liable for any items that might be lost in transit or don’t arrive if you have chosen a different shipping method. All returns must be sent back as a single shipment. Please make sure to insure your jewelry for the value that was paid. You are responsible for the insurance fees of the return shipment.</p>
                                        <p>We will be more than happy to assist you. Simply send us an email to order@smilingrocks.com and we will walk you through all the details.</p>
                                    </div>
                                    <div class="oandD">
                                        <p class="pque">Will I be refunded the full amount I paid?</p>
                                        <p>Items approved for return, we will refund back within a week once it is approved. The item will be refunded to your original payment method. It may take 10 days for your designated banks to post the funds to your account. For PayPal, it takes around 2 weeks for the refund to be processed to your account. Items with special order or request are not refundable.</p>
                                    </div>
                                    <div class="oandD">
                                        <p class="pque">What are the supported Payment Methods?</p>
                                        <p>You can complete your purchase through the payment ways below:</p>
                                        <ul>
                                            <li>Mastercard</li>
                                            <li>Visa</li>
                                            <li>PayPal</li>
                                            <li>American Express</li>
                                            <li>Apple Pay</li>
                                        </ul>
                                    </div>                                      
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="firstpoint">
                                <div class="poinTitle">
                                    <h2>Lifetime Warranty</h2>
                                </div>
                                <div class="detail">
                                    <div class="oandD">
                                        <p>Be rest assured with your Smiling Rocks jewelry! We will provide you with Lifetime Warranty guarantee with any jewelry purchased from Smiling Rocks. If you believe your item has any manufacturing defect, you can ship it to us with your proof of purchase for us to inspect. If we determine the jewelry damage is valid, we will repair the item.</p>
                                        <p>The type of repairs included are:</p>
                                        <ul>
                                            <li>Complimentary polishing of jewelry</li>
                                            <li>Complimentary resizing one size up or down (Eternity bands are not resizable).</li>
                                            <li>If your diamond falls out you can return it to us and we do our best to reset it. But if the diamond is lost, we are unable to replace it with a new one. You would need to purchase a diamond for replacing it.</li>    
                                        </ul>
                                        <p>Our repair policy excludes wear and tear, loss of diamonds, product loss or item being stolen and any repairs or work not done by Smiling Rocks will void this warranty. For a repair request, we will first need to receive a proof of purchase shipped together with the jewelry. If the repair request is aligned with our policy, we will proceed with the request. If it is not, we will notify you if the repair service is available and what it will cost. The repaired items will be delivered back to your given shipping address in one to two weeks’ time. We offer complimentary shipping back to the customers for all warrantied repairs.</p>
                                    </div>
                                    <div class="oandD">
                                        <p class="pque">Special Order Request</p>
                                        <p class="pque">I’d like to engrave my name on my jewelry, can I do so?</p>
                                        <p>Yes! But we can only engrave your initials on your jewelry.  If you have purchased our Smiling Rocks jewelry and wish to engrave your initials on it, we are happy to help you do so. Email us at order@smilingrocks.com and with proof of purchase for us to confirm and proceed with your request.</p>
                                    </div>
                                    <div class="oandD">
                                        <p class="pque">In what Karat gold is done Smiling Rocks jewelry?</p>
                                        <p>10K gold. If you wish to place any of our favorite order in a different metal purity (14K or 18K), email us at order@smilingrocks.com and we will look into your request.</p>
                                        <p>All special orders are not refundable or returnable. They will take around 2 weeks’ time to deliver from the date of purchase.</p>
                                    </div>                                    
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="firstpoint">
                                <div class="poinTitle">
                                    <h2>Account Support</h2>
                                </div>
                                <div class="detail">
                                    <div class="oandD">
                                        <p class="pque">How do I create an account?</p>
                                        <p>To create an account simply click the Sign In button and Register Now to fill in your details. Please create an account password which is unique and kept secure. You must notify Smiling Rocks immediately of any unauthorized use of your account.</p>
                                        <p>With a Smiling Rocks account you will be able to enjoy the following benefits:</p>
                                        <ul>    
                                            <li>Preview our new collections</li>
                                            <li>Track your orders and review your order history</li>
                                            <li>Save your address and card details so you can make the purchase process much easier and faster</li>
                                        </ul>
                                    </div>
                                    <div class="oandD">
                                        <p class="pque">I need help to login to  My Account:</p>
                                        <p>If you are experiencing any issues to login into your account, please don’t hesitate to contact our Customer Support team at order@smilingrocks.com and we will assist you with any questions.</p>
                                    </div>     
                                    <div class="oandD">
                                        <p class="pque">How do I restore my account password?</p>
                                        <p>To reset your password, follow the 'FORGOT  YOUR PASSWORD' instructions on the SIGN IN page. Please note, for security reasons we are unable to send your old password via email.</p>
                                        <p><em><bold>If you have any more questions for us, feel free to contact us at order@smilingrocks.com. Shop with a Smile!</bold></em></p>
                                    </div>                                  
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>      
        </t>
    </template>
    
    
    
    <record id="faq_page" model="website.page">
        <field name="name">Frequently Asked Questions</field>
        <field name="is_published" eval="True"/>
        <field name="url">/pages/lab-grown-diamond-frequently-asked-questions</field>
        <field name="header_overlay" eval="True"/>
        <field name="view_id" ref="faq_test"/>
        <field name="track" eval="True"/>
    </record>
</odoo>